

# **YOUNES SHEIKHLAR**

Web developer & Mobile

#### **Technical Skills:**

- HTML, CSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap5
- JavaScript , TypeScript
- React.js , Node.js
- MongoDB
- React-native- Mobile



Rue Des Veterinaires 26 Anderlecht / Brussels / Belgium



0471823827



sheikhlaryounes@gmail.com



https://vounessheikhlar.vercel.api



## **Professional summary**

After few years as a pharmacy assistant, I have decided to switch to a new career path . By joining <@Be Code />.

I have gained experience in basic website design issues such as TML, CSS, and Javascript . I have also worked with frameworks and libraries, which include:

Bootstrap, Tailwind, React.js, Next.js, Docker. React-native

I have also completed my internship.

# **Professional Experience**

WEB DEVELOPER

#### **BECODE**

Becode is a bootcamp with active pedagogy

Here are few of my project:

- Joinsmile : a startup to deliver medicine from pharmacy to customers. And I was present in this project as a front end developer
- younicoin: Website to see the price of cryptocurrencies ( react.js , API , Node.js Express.js)
- Sj84-watchface: A website and platform that allows users to create and customize smartwatches for their website.

### Github:

https://github.com/Younes-sh

#### **Asistant Pharmacist**

Maryam Pharmacy 2007-2016

- perscription OTC
- stock management

# **Quality manager**

SUPA 2005-2007

supervising suture thread quality

### **Education**

### **TECHNOFUTUR TIC:**

Javascript 31 Jaunuary 2022 / 14 March 2022

HIGH SCHOOL: imam khomeyni 2000 - 2003